bobibanking.com 2019-01-21

# PRIVACY POLICY

**PRIVACY POLICY** ****

**The information of customers and others who visit the Bank's website we believe it is necessary to post a privacy statement. The information shared with the Bank will be treated as private. We also desire to say explicitly that adequate precautions have been taken to protect information relating to customers and their dealings with the Bank from the mischievous and the fraudsters.sters.**

**The Bank has adopted the privacy policy aimed at protecting the personal information entrusted and disclosed by the customers.This policy governs the way in which the Bank collects, uses, discloses, stores, secures and disposes of personal information and sensitive personal data or information.**

**The Bank collects and uses the financial information and other personal information from its customers. This information is collected and used for specific business purposes or for other related purposes designated by the Bank or for a lawful purpose to comply with the applicable laws and regulations. The Bank shall not divulge any personal information collected from the customer, for cross selling or any other purposes.**

**The authenticity of the personal information provided by the customer shall not be the responsibility of the Bank. Any information that is freely available or accessible in public domain or furnished under the Right to Information Act, 2005 or any other law for the time being in force shall not be regarded as personal information for the purposes of this Policy and the Bank shall not be responsible for the same.**

**Bank endeavours to safeguard and ensure the security of the information provided by the Customer. Bank uses 128-bit encryption, for the transmission of the information, which is currently the permitted level of encryption in India. When the information provided by the Customers is not transmitted through this encryption, the Customers' system (if configured accordingly) will display an appropriate message ensuring the best level of secrecy for the Customer's information.**

**The Customer would be required to cooperate with Bank in order to ensure the security of the information, and it is recommended that the Customers necessarily choose their passwords carefully such that no unauthorised access is made by a third party. To make the password complex and difficult for others to guess, the Customers should use combination of alphabets, numbers and special characters (like #,$,@, &,%). The Customers should undertake not to disclose their password to anyone or keep any written or other record of the password such that a third party could access it.**

**Bank undertakes not to disclose the information provided by the Customers to any person, unless such action is necessary to:**

  * **Conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process;**
  * **Protect and defend Bank's or its Affiliates' rights, interests or property;**
  * **Enforce the terms and conditions of the products or services or;**
  * **Act to protect the interests of Bank, its Affiliates, or its members, constituents or of other persons.**

***************

**Cookie policy** ****

**Cookies are a kind of short term memory for the web. They are stored in your browser and enable a site to 'remember' little bits of information between pages or visits.**

**They are widely used to make the web experience more personal, which is generally seen as a positive thing. However some cookies collect data across many websites, creating 'behavioural profiles' of people. These profiles can then be used to decide what content or adverts to show you. This use of cookies for targeting in particular is what the law was designed to highlight. By requiring websites to inform and obtain consent from visitors it aims to give web users more control over their online privacy.Cookies are used for lots of tasks like remembering your preferences & settings, provide personalized browsing experience and analyze site operations. These cookies collect information about how users use a website, for instance, how often visited pages. All information collected by third party cookies is aggregated and anonymous. By using our website user/s agree that these types of cookies can be placed on his/her device. User/s is free to disable/delete these cookies by changing his/her device / browser settings. Axis Bank is not responsible for cookies placed in the device of user/s by any other website and information collected thereto.**

**How we use, collect, and retain customer information**

**We collect and retain information about you only for specific business purposes.**

**How does Bank use Cookies?**

**Bank uses cookies to capture following information –**

  * **Source of visit to the website**
  * **Time spent on the website**
  * **Pages viewed on the website**

**How we restrict the disclosure of customer information**

**Bank does not release customer information except as directed by law or as per your mandate. We do not share specific information about customer accounts or other personally identifiable data with nonaffiliated third parties for their independent use unless:**

  * **The information is provided to help complete a transaction initiated by you;**
  * **You request or authorize it;**
  * **The disclosure is required by/or directed by law; or**
  * **You have been informed about the possibility of such disclosure for marketing or similar purposes through a prior communication and have been given the opportunity to decline.**

**Notice of change**

**The Bank may, from time to time, change this Policy. The effective date of this Policy, as stated below, indicates the last time this Policy was revised or materially changed.**
